<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PhyloTips: Tips for those using phylogenies in their work</title>
    <link>https://phylotips.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PhyloTips: Tips for those using phylogenies in their work</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://phylotips.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://phylotips.info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phylotips.info/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAUP batch files</title>
      <link>https://phylotips.info/post/paup-batch-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phylotips.info/post/paup-batch-files/</guid>
      <description>This is a backup courtesy of the Internet Archive’s Wayback Machine of a page I made shortly after graduate school with batch files for PAUP. May they be of some utility to you.
Phylogenetic analysis Each item includes PAUP batch files or commands where appropriate. I wrote this page for the Farrell Lab website, but have included it here as well. This page is mostly useful for the batch files which are on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to this site</title>
      <link>https://phylotips.info/post/intro-to-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phylotips.info/post/intro-to-this-site/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to PhyloTips.info. From teaching my PhyloMeth course and working with students and colleagues in general, as well as the great example of Liam Revell’s Phytools Blog, I decided to make a site where I could post tips to deal with problems of people working on phylogenies. Since I mostly use R for this (though this may change as Julia, Python, etc. grow)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My ultrametric tree is not ultrametric</title>
      <link>https://phylotips.info/post/my-ultrametric-tree-is-not-ultrametric/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://phylotips.info/post/my-ultrametric-tree-is-not-ultrametric/</guid>
      <description>Getting a tree with branch lengths proportional to time is a key step for many methods. With NSF’s generous assistance, we’re working on methods to make this easier (the Datelife.org website, the datelife R package), but one can look for chronograms at TreeBase and Open Tree of Life, or even make your own using r8s, treepl, Beast, RevBayes, or more. The convention in phylogenetics is to call trees with equal root to tip lengths “ultrametric.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>